{
  "author": "ramseyfox",
  "rounds": [
    {
      "roundTitle": "Please Choose an Egyptian Hieroglyph",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Head of Egyptian Deity Re (or Ra)",
          "correctAnswer": "Falcon with Sun on Head"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Aslan, for instance",
          "correctAnswer": "Lion"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Venomous member of the genus Cerastes",
          "correctAnswer": "Horned Viper"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Featured in first Elton John U.S. Number 1 single",
          "correctAnswer": "Crocodile"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "National bird of Israel",
          "correctAnswer": "Hoopoe"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Are grey at first, gaining color due to beta-carotene in their diet",
          "correctAnswer": "Flamingo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Feature of the annual 'Encierros de San Fermin'",
          "correctAnswer": "Charging Bull"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Shakira's character in Zootopia/Zootropolis",
          "correctAnswer": "Gazelle"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Symbol of the U.S. Republican Party",
          "correctAnswer": "Elephant"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Eighth biblical Plague of Egypt",
          "correctAnswer": "Locust"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Geoffrey, the mascot of Toys ''R'' Us",
          "correctAnswer": "Giraffe"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Zodiac symbol of someone born on 1 January",
          "correctAnswer": "Goat"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Jackal Looking Back",
        "Ibis",
        "Erect Cobra",
        "Donkey",
        "Cat",
        "Fly",
        "Scorpion",
        "Vulture with Flail"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "What Comes Fourth in this Sequence?",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Red, Orange, Yellow, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Green"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Yellow (2), Green (3), Brown (4), _____ (5)?",
          "correctAnswer": "Blue"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Mustard, Peacock, Plum, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Scarlet"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Green, Hazel, Blue, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Brown"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Key (Black), Yellow, Magenta, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Cyan"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Maroon, Brick, Ruby, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Red"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Pallet, Viridian, Pewter, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Cerulean"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Red (22°N), Yellow (38°N), Black (44°N), _____ (65°N)?",
          "correctAnswer": "White"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Lead, Thallium, Mercury, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Gold"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Light Blue, Pink, White, _____?",
          "correctAnswer": "Pink"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Green ($/£ 920), Yellow ($/£ 800), Red ($/£ 680), _____ ($/£ 560)?",
          "correctAnswer": "Orange"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "White, Cyan (-FF), Blue (-FF), _____ (-FF)?",
          "correctAnswer": "Black"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Yellow",
        "Indigo",
        "Purple",
        "Silver"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Anyway, Here's Water Wall",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Disney's 'Blizzard Beach' or 'Typhoon Lagoon'",
          "correctAnswer": "Water Park"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "1990s political scandal featuring President Clinton",
          "correctAnswer": "Whitewater"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Subtitle to the 2022 Avatar sequel",
          "correctAnswer": "The Way of Water"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Nicknamed the 'Poor Man's Bread' in Victorian England",
          "correctAnswer": "Watercress"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Vinnufallet in Norway, one of the Top 10 Tallest in the World",
          "correctAnswer": "Waterfall"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Invented in 13th century Italy",
          "correctAnswer": "Watermark"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "In finance, owing more on a mortgage than the property is worth",
          "correctAnswer": "Underwater"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Variety of taffy created in 1880s New Jersey",
          "correctAnswer": "Salt Water"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Subject of around 250 Monet paintings",
          "correctAnswer": "Water Lilies"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Watergate",
        "Waterbed",
        "The Shape of Water",
        "Water Slide",
        "Watercolour",
        "Mineral Water",
        "Watermelon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "ND TH SCR GS T",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the six films that won the Academy Award for Best Picture",
          "correctAnswer": "CSBLNC"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the six films that won the Academy Award for Best Picture",
          "correctAnswer": "MDS"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the six films that won the Academy Award for Best Picture",
          "correctAnswer": "RG"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the six films that won the Academy Award for Best Picture",
          "correctAnswer": "PRST"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the six films that won the Academy Award for Best Picture",
          "correctAnswer": "R NMN"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the six films that won the Academy Award for Best Picture",
          "correctAnswer": "LWRN CF RB"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "T HWZR DF Z",
        "LL L ND",
        "RGN GBLL",
        "JWS",
        "MLN RG",
        "P",
        "LF F P",
        "FRG",
        "F WG DM N",
        "GHST"
      ]
    }
  ]
}